bobinoz.com 2016-10-13

# Privacy Policy

## Web Products Pty Ltd  
WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY

BobinOz.com is owned by Web Products Pty Ltd, ABN 53 131 039 346

Web Products Pty Ltd, (referred to sometimes in this document as “COMPANY” or “We”), is concerned that its reputation, and the responsibilities that come with using it, always remain of paramount importance in all of Web Products Pty Ltd’s activities.

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Web Products Pty Ltd’s policy is to respect the privacy of all of our visitors, so the following policy statement tells you about what information we may receive, send or ask of you, what its used for and ways you can control its use.

Generally, anyone can come to visit BobinOz.com, and Web Products Pty Ltd will not keep information about these visits except for a record of how many total visits have been made to the Website and its various web pages altogether (not how many times any single person has visited).

However, if you become a Customer/Member which requires giving identifying information to Web Products Pty Ltd (together referred to in this document as a “Customer/Member “), Membership records will be started according to information you give us or that we receive from or send to your computer.

**SECURITY**

Web Products Pty Ltd has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honoured. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties.  
Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except as required by law or as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy and in our Terms of Use. You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can share these see or edit your personal information without knowing your user name and password, so do not with others.

**ENFORCEMENT**

If for some reason you believe Web Products Pty Ltd has not adhered to these principles, please notify us at: bob@bobinoz.com or by certified mail, return receipt requested, to PO Box 1042 Kenmore QLD 4070 Australia. We will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.

**WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION YOU SHARE**

When you join us, you provide us with your contact information, including your name and email address. We use this information to send you updates about your order, questionnaires to measure your satisfaction with our service and announcements about new and exciting services that we offer. When you order from us, our 3rd party payment processors such as PayPal and 2checkout.com will ask for your credit card number and billing address. They use this information only to bill you for the product(s) you order at that time.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including programming, answering Customer/Member questions about products or services, sending email and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

**CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, Web Products Pty Ltd will not share your personal information with any third parties without your consent.

Web Products Pty Ltd will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

i. Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Web Products Pty Ltd or the site;

ii. Protect and defend the rights or property of Web Products Pty Ltd and its family of Websites;

iii. Enforce our Terms of Use Agreement [insert hyperlink here]; or

iv. Act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of the Site.

**DO YOU ACCEPT OUR PRIVACY POLICY?**

By using this Web Site, you are verifying that you agree to, and will abide by, the terms of the Web Products Pty Ltd Privacy Policy.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO DO SO, STOP VISITING OUR WEB SITES.

Second, check our privacy policy every once in a while. Certain things may change over time, and we may include new information and privacy policies that will be placed in this document. If you continue to visit Web Products Pty Ltd after any such changes, you will again be verifying that you agree to, and will abide by, the current privacy policy, as it then exists.

**UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site.

**QUESTIONS & COMMENTS? **

Web Products Pty Ltd is always ready to review your questions and comments and we will attempt to give you our best responses. Remember, we have a lot of Customers/Members and other visitors to respond to as well, but we will try to reply as promptly and thoroughly as possible. To contact Web Products Pty Ltd about our privacy policy, send an email to bob@bobinoz.com.

_5 July 2011_

It's good to share...000000
